Was this the great cause
you faced back then?
Mo'er,
the most vicious poison in the world
is not arsenic or poisoned wine,
but trampling on human lives
in the name of immortality
and great causes.
Deputy Director Shen,
come with me to Ci'en Temple today.
Director,
the smell of this water is not an ordinary ritual item.
Deputy Director Shen,
this is the Soul-Soothing Soup.
It can cleanse the dust in your heart.
During today's ritual,
why not give it a try?
I have duties to attend to,
so I need to stay awake and observe.
I dare not be distracted.
Over 300 people,
30% have already drunk it.
Her forehead is glowing.
Director,
I feel a bit stuffy.
May I excuse myself for a moment?
Go ahead.
There is a quiet room in the back hall.
This is a restricted area.
Trespassers will be killed.
I am the Deputy Director of the Imperial Astronomical Bureau,
currently inspecting the temple.
Stop.
Deputy Director Shen,
please follow me.
These are relics of eminent monks,
the core for transferring soul power.
These medicinal materials
are identical to the ingredients of the Soul-Locking Pill in the Black Tower.
That's right.
The holy water is brewed with this,
and a special primer is added.
The holy water contains hallucinogens and egg-like soul seeds.
Ci'en Temple is a soul power farm.
A soul power transmission pipeline.
The ritual is about to end.
We should go back.
Deputy Director Shen,
what you saw today
is top secret.
I will keep my mouth shut.
Soul-Devouring Gu.
Its eggs are as small as dust
and dissolve in water.
It can control the mind.
It's Zhang Min.
I'm being watched.
Fixed step spacing.
Standard signs of a drug-controlled person.
Stop.